[
    { "id": "1x1", "front": "1 x 1", "back": "1"},
    { "id": "2x1", "front": "2 x 1", "back": "2"},
    { "id": "3x1", "front": "3 x 1", "back": "3"},
    { "id": "4x1", "front": "4 x 1", "back": "4"},
    { "id": "5x1", "front": "5 x 1", "back": "5"},
    { "id": "6x1", "front": "6 x 1", "back": "6"},
    { "id": "7x1", "front": "7 x 1", "back": "7"},
    { "id": "8x1", "front": "8 x 1", "back": "8"},
    { "id": "9x1", "front": "9 x 1", "back": "9"},
    { "id": "10x1", "front": "10 x 1", "back": "10"},
    { "id": "1x2", "front": "1 x 2", "back": "2"},
    { "id": "2x2", "front": "2 x 2", "back": "4"},
    { "id": "3x2", "front": "3 x 2", "back": "6"},
    { "id": "4x2", "front": "4 x 2", "back": "8"},
    { "id": "5x2", "front": "5 x 2", "back": "10"},
    { "id": "6x2", "front": "6 x 2", "back": "12"},
    { "id": "7x2", "front": "7 x 2", "back": "14"},
    { "id": "8x2", "front": "8 x 2", "back": "16"},
    { "id": "9x2", "front": "9 x 2", "back": "18"},
    { "id": "10x2", "front": "10 x 2", "back": "20"},
    { "id": "1x3", "front": "1 x 3", "back": "3"},
    { "id": "2x3", "front": "2 x 3", "back": "6"},
    { "id": "3x3", "front": "3 x 3", "back": "9"},
    { "id": "4x3", "front": "4 x 3", "back": "12"},
    { "id": "5x3", "front": "5 x 3", "back": "15"},
    { "id": "6x3", "front": "6 x 3", "back": "18"},
    { "id": "7x3", "front": "7 x 3", "back": "21"},
    { "id": "8x3", "front": "8 x 3", "back": "24"},
    { "id": "9x3", "front": "9 x 3", "back": "27"},
    { "id": "10x3", "front": "10 x 3", "back": "30"},
    { "id": "1x4", "front": "1 x 4", "back": "4"},
    { "id": "2x4", "front": "2 x 4", "back": "8"},
    { "id": "3x4", "front": "3 x 4", "back": "12"},
    { "id": "4x4", "front": "4 x 4", "back": "16"},
    { "id": "5x4", "front": "5 x 4", "back": "20"},
    { "id": "6x4", "front": "6 x 4", "back": "24"},
    { "id": "7x4", "front": "7 x 4", "back": "28"},
    { "id": "8x4", "front": "8 x 4", "back": "32"},
    { "id": "9x4", "front": "9 x 4", "back": "36"},
    { "id": "10x4", "front": "10 x 4", "back": "40"},
    { "id": "1x5", "front": "1 x 5", "back": "5"},
    { "id": "2x5", "front": "2 x 5", "back": "10"},
    { "id": "3x5", "front": "3 x 5", "back": "15"},
    { "id": "4x5", "front": "4 x 5", "back": "20"},
    { "id": "5x5", "front": "5 x 5", "back": "25"},
    { "id": "6x5", "front": "6 x 5", "back": "30"},
    { "id": "7x5", "front": "7 x 5", "back": "35"},
    { "id": "8x5", "front": "8 x 5", "back": "40"},
    { "id": "9x5", "front": "9 x 5", "back": "45"},
    { "id": "10x5", "front": "10 x 5", "back": "50"},
    { "id": "1x6", "front": "1 x 6", "back": "6"},
    { "id": "2x6", "front": "2 x 6", "back": "12"},
    { "id": "3x6", "front": "3 x 6", "back": "18"},
    { "id": "4x6", "front": "4 x 6", "back": "24"},
    { "id": "5x6", "front": "5 x 6", "back": "30"},
    { "id": "6x6", "front": "6 x 6", "back": "36"},
    { "id": "7x6", "front": "7 x 6", "back": "42"},
    { "id": "8x6", "front": "8 x 6", "back": "48"},
    { "id": "9x6", "front": "9 x 6", "back": "54"},
    { "id": "10x6", "front": "10 x 6", "back": "60"},
    { "id": "1x7", "front": "1 x 7", "back": "7"},
    { "id": "2x7", "front": "2 x 7", "back": "14"},
    { "id": "3x7", "front": "3 x 7", "back": "21"},
    { "id": "4x7", "front": "4 x 7", "back": "28"},
    { "id": "5x7", "front": "5 x 7", "back": "35"},
    { "id": "6x7", "front": "6 x 7", "back": "42"},
    { "id": "7x7", "front": "7 x 7", "back": "49"},
    { "id": "8x7", "front": "8 x 7", "back": "56"},
    { "id": "9x7", "front": "9 x 7", "back": "63"},
    { "id": "10x7", "front": "10 x 7", "back": "70"},
    { "id": "1x8", "front": "1 x 8", "back": "8"},
    { "id": "2x8", "front": "2 x 8", "back": "16"},
    { "id": "3x8", "front": "3 x 8", "back": "24"},
    { "id": "4x8", "front": "4 x 8", "back": "32"},
    { "id": "5x8", "front": "5 x 8", "back": "40"},
    { "id": "6x8", "front": "6 x 8", "back": "48"},
    { "id": "7x8", "front": "7 x 8", "back": "56"},
    { "id": "8x8", "front": "8 x 8", "back": "64"},
    { "id": "9x8", "front": "9 x 8", "back": "72"},
    { "id": "10x8", "front": "10 x 8", "back": "80"},
    { "id": "1x9", "front": "1 x 9", "back": "9"},
    { "id": "2x9", "front": "2 x 9", "back": "18"},
    { "id": "3x9", "front": "3 x 9", "back": "27"},
    { "id": "4x9", "front": "4 x 9", "back": "36"},
    { "id": "5x9", "front": "5 x 9", "back": "45"},
    { "id": "6x9", "front": "6 x 9", "back": "54"},
    { "id": "7x9", "front": "7 x 9", "back": "63"},
    { "id": "8x9", "front": "8 x 9", "back": "72"},
    { "id": "9x9", "front": "9 x 9", "back": "81"},
    { "id": "10x9", "front": "10 x 9", "back": "90"},
    { "id": "1x10", "front": "1 x 10", "back": "10"},
    { "id": "2x10", "front": "2 x 10", "back": "20"},
    { "id": "3x10", "front": "3 x 10", "back": "30"},
    { "id": "4x10", "front": "4 x 10", "back": "40"},
    { "id": "5x10", "front": "5 x 10", "back": "50"},
    { "id": "6x10", "front": "6 x 10", "back": "60"},
    { "id": "7x10", "front": "7 x 10", "back": "70"},
    { "id": "8x10", "front": "8 x 10", "back": "80"},
    { "id": "9x10", "front": "9 x 10", "back": "90"},
    { "id": "10x10", "front": "10 x 10", "back": "100"}
]

